### Privacy Policy of Call Blocker – block incoming and outgoing calls

[](https://www.call-blocker.info/home)Privacy Policy of Call Blocker – block incoming and outgoing calls

This Application Collect and/or Shares some Personal Data from its Users.
-------------------------------------------------------------------------

**INTRODUCTION**

Applika GmbH. (“Applika”, “our”, “we”, “us” or the “Company”) is committed to respect the privacy and Personal Information of the users (“user” or “you”) in connection with the use of our mobile application and/or by accessing our website [https://call-blocker.info](https://call-blocker.info/) (collectively the “Service”).

Policy summary

Personal data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**Analytics:**

Google Analytics with anonymized IP.

**Personal Data:** Cookies and Usage Data

**Device permissions:** 

Contacts permission (Mandatory),

Phone permission (Mandatory),

Call Log permission (Mandatory),

SMS permission (Not mandatory),

Approximate location permission (Not mandatory),

Precise location permission (Not mandatory)

**Contacting the User:**

Contact form.

**Specific Personal Information we collect Or that they collect third-party companies:**

Your full name, phone number and email address, payment information, the Google log-in details, information stored on your device phonebook directory (e.g. phone number, email address and name of your contacts), your approximate geolocation (via Wi-Fi or cellular technology in your device, including, country), internet protocol (IP) address and other unique device identifiers and descriptions, and any other information that you will decide to provide/supply us with.

**Infrastructure monitoring:**

Firebase Crashlytics, Google Play Services, AdMob, Firebase Analytics.

Full policy

Owner and Data Controller
-------------------------

Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collect or shares, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies, Usage Data, Android User ID, Email, Approximate location, Precise location.

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.  
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using this Application.  
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by this Application is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services. In cases where this Application specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.  
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Application or by the owners of third-party services used by this Application serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through this Application and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

**We may use third-party companies to serve services when you use the Application:**

These companies may use information about your visits to the Application and other websites that are contained in web cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

One of those partners is **AppVestor**, whom respects the users fundamental legal rights to data protection and privacy. Click on the following link to access AppVestor’s Privacy Policy ([https://legal.appvestor.com/privacy-policy/](https://legal.appvestor.com/privacy-policy/)) and End-User License Agreement ([https://legal.appvestor.com/end-user-license-agreement/](https://legal.appvestor.com/end-user-license-agreement/)).

**Enhanced Caller ID**

The Enhanced Caller ID feature is provided by [**Sync.me Technologies Ltd**](http://sync.me/). (“Sync.me”).

**If you choose to activate the Enhanced Caller ID feature**, **[Sync.me](http://sync.me/) will collect information in accordance with its [Privacy Policy](https://sync.me/privacy).** You can opt-out by clicking on the following link: [Sync.me Opt-Out](https://sync.me/unsubscribe).

Transfer of Your Data

Your Personal Data (the advertiser ID and unique ID regarding consent), may be processed in any place where Our Data Partners are located. It means that this information may be transferred to — and maintained on — servers located outside of Your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those of Your jurisdiction.

If Your data is transferred to a country outside the EU/EEA, and if the country in question has not been approved by the European Commission as providing adequate protection ([See list of adequacy decisions here](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions_en)) Our data transfers will be based on [Standard Contractual Clauses](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc_en) (SCC) also approved by the European Commission.

Furthermore, we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of Your data and other personal information.

We have agreements with the following Data Partners. These third-party vendors collect, store, use, process, and transfer information about Your activity on Our Service in accordance with their own Privacy Policies. We are currently partnered with the following Data Partners who all act as independent Data Controllers to whom Your data will be transferred:

**AdMob Ads network (Google)** [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

**Firebase Analytics (Google)** [Privacy Policy](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy?hl=en)

**Equativ Ads network** [privacy policy](https://equativ.com/end-users-privacy-policy/)

**Applovin Ads network** [privacy policy](https://www.applovin.com/privacy/)

**Unity Ads network** [privacy policy](https://unity.com/legal/game-player-and-app-user-privacy-policy)

All of Our Service Providers reserve the right to use and merge the transferred information for statistics, customizing ads in apps and other advertising, and user support without restrictions regarding applicability in time and in accordance with their stated privacy policy.

We will therefore only transfer data with Your specific consent.

Mode and place of processing the Data
-------------------------------------

**Methods of processing**

The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of this Application (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

**Legal basis of processing**

The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

* Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;

1. provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
2. processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
3. processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
4. processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.

In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

**Place**

The Data is processed at the Owner’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.

Depending on the User’s location, data transfers may involve transferring the User’s Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.

**Retention time**

Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for.

Therefore:

* Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
* Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.

The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.

Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

The purposes of processing
--------------------------

Why is the Personal Information collected and for what purposes? We collect the Personal Information for the purpose of: (i) allowing you to create your account, (ii) allowing you to log in to the App, (iii) allowing you to enjoy features available to registered users only, (iv) to complete the registration, we may contact you with the number your provided us (via inbound call or SMS) in order to authenticate your identity and prevent fraud, (v) when using our Name Tag feature – when sufficient number of users indicated that the phone number is associated with the same name, the name and phone number will be included in our directory, (vi) to match the information in your phone and contacts with numbers from the calls you make or receive, as well as with information in our database. We also store this information for subsequent data validation for both you and other users of our App and other products (vii) to send you push notifications, for example, to remind you and/or suggest you to sync your contacts, (viii) to enhance and personalize your experience and customize the advertising content we display, and (ix) to communicate with you (via email, mobile device, etc.) and to authenticate your identity, (x) to perform research, technical diagnostics, analytics or statistical purposes; (xi) to provide you with the most relevant additional services and offers, and (xii) some information will be processed on our directory and allow you to perform numeric search and identify incoming calls against this directory, which contains the contacts’ information of users who permitted the process of this information.

Data shared

Data that may be shared with other companies or organizations. 

Data shared and for what purpose:

 **Location**

Approximate location and Precise location

**Approximate location**

Analytics, Advertising or marketing

**Precise location**

Analytics, Advertising or marketing

 **App activity**

App interactions

**App interactions Data shared and for what purpose**

Analytics

**App info and performance**

Crash logs, Diagnostics, and Other app performance data

**Crash logs**

Analytics

**Diagnostics**

Analytics

**Other app performance data**

Analytics

 **Device or other IDs**

Device or other IDs

**Device or other IDs**

Analytics, Advertising or marketing

**Phonebook Contacts (optional, not mandatory)**

Service improvement. Application features.

Device permissions for Personal Data access
-------------------------------------------

Depending on the User’s specific device, this Application may request certain permissions that allow it to access the User’s device Data as described below.

By default, these permissions must be granted by the User before the respective information can be accessed. Once the permission has been given, it can be revoked by the User at any time. In order to revoke these permissions, Users may refer to the device settings or contact the Owner for support at the contact details provided in the present document.  
The exact procedure for controlling app permissions may be dependent on the User’s device and software.

Please note that the revoking of such permissions might impact the proper functioning of this Application.

If User grants any of the permissions listed below, the respective Personal Data may be processed (i.e accessed to, modified or removed) by this Application.

**Contacts permission(mandatory)**

Used for accessing contacts and profiles on the User’s device, including the changing of entries.

**Phone permission(mandatory)**

Used for accessing a host of typical features associated with telephony. This enables, for instance, read-only access to the “phone state”, which means it enables access to the phone number of the device, current mobile network information, or the status of any ongoing calls.

**Call Log permission(mandatory)**

Used for accessing call log on the User’s device, including the changing of entries.

**SMS permission(not mandatory)**

Used to send SMS in response to the caller

**Approximate location(not mandatory)**

Provide additional services and information, related to the user’s location. Such as weather, news, etc.

**Precise location(not mandatory)**

Provide additional services and information, related to the user’s location. Such as weather, news, etc.

Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data
-------------------------------------------------------

**Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:**

**Contacting the User –** **Contact form (this Application)**

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes this Application to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.

Personal Data collected: e-mail

**Infrastructure monitoring**

**Firebase Analytics**. We also use “Google Analytics for Firebase”. By enabling this tool, we enable the collection of data about App Users, including via identifiers for mobile devices (including Android Advertising ID and Advertising Identifier for iOS), cookies and similar technologies. We use the information we get from Google Analytics for Firebase to maintain and improve our App(s). We do not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information unless we have robust notice of, and your prior affirmative (i.e., opt-in) consent to, that merger. Finally, please note that Google Analytics for Firebase’s terms (available at [https://firebase.google.com/terms/](https://firebase.google.com/terms/)) shall also apply.

**Advertising Partners**. Through our services, we allow third party advertising partners to set technologies and other tracking tools to collect information regarding your activities and your device (e.g., your IP address, mobile identifiers, page(s) visited, location, time of day). We also combine and share such information and other information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) with third party advertising partners. These advertising partners will use this information (and similar information collected from other websites) for purposes of delivering targeted advertisements to you when you visit third party websites within their networks. This practice is commonly referred to as “interest-based advertising” or “online behavioral advertising. We allow access to other data collected by the services to share information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you. If you prefer not to share your Personal Information with third party advertising partners, you may let us know.

We reserve the right to remove or add new analytic tools.

The rights of Users
-------------------

Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following:

**Withdraw their consent at any time.** Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.

**Object to processing of their Data.** Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.

**Access their Data.** Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.

**Verify and seek rectification.** Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.

**Restrict the processing of their Data.** Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.

**Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed.** Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.

**Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller.** Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User’s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.

**Lodge a complaint.** Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

**Details about the right to object to processing**

Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.

Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

**How to exercise these rights**

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.

**Additional information about Data collection and processing**

**Legal action**

The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related Services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

**Additional information about User’s Personal Data**

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

**System logs and maintenance**

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.

**Information not contained in this policy**

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

**How “Do Not Track” requests are handled**

This Application does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within this Application and/or – as far as technically and legally feasible – sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.

Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

Definitions and legal references
--------------------------------

**Personal Data (or Data)**

Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

**Usage Data**

Information collected automatically through this Application (or third-party services employed in this Application), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.

**User**

The individual using this Application who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

**Data Subject**

The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

**Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)**

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

**Data Controller (or Owner)**

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application.

**This Application**

The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

**Service**

The service provided by this Application as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

**European Union (or EU)**

Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.

**Cookies**

Small sets of data stored in the User’s device.

* * *

**Legal information**

This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).

This privacy policy relates solely to this Application, if not stated otherwise within this document.

**For Users Within the European Economic Area (EEA)**

Applika GmbH undertakes to respect the confidentiality of Your Data and to guarantee You can exercise Your rights.

You have the right under this Privacy Policy, and by law, if You are within the European Union (EU), to:

* **Access Your Personal Data** and update or delete the information We have on You. Please contact Us to assist You.
* **Correct the Personal Data that We hold about You.** You have the right to have any incomplete or inaccurate information We hold about You corrected.
* **Object to the processing of Your Personal Data.**. This right exists where We are relying on legitimate interest as the legal basis for Our processing and there is something about Your particular situation, which makes You want to object to Our processing of Your Personal Data on this ground. You also have the right to object to where We are processing Your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes.
* **Erasure.** You have the right to ask Us to delete or remove Personal Data when there is no good reason for Us to continue processing it.
* **Request the transfer of Your Personal Data.** We will provide to You, or to a third party You have chosen, Your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Please note that this right only applies to automated information which You initially provided consent for Us to use or where We used the information to perform a contract with You.
* **Withdraw Your consent.** You have the right to withdraw Your consent on using Your Personal Data. If You withdraw Your consent, We may not be able to provide You with access to certain specific functionalities of the Service.

You may exercise Your rights of access, rectification, cancellation, and opposition by contacting Us. Users can exercise their rights to prevent processing by contacting Applika GmbH at [privacy@applika.ch](mailto:privacy@applika.ch). Please note that We may ask You to verify Your identity before responding to such requests.

**PIPA** – For users in South Korea

**Deletion of Your Data**

All data that has fulfilled its purposes will be identified by Applika GmbH and deleted without delay in accordance with this privacy policy. Applika GmbH will take all commercially and technologically reasonable measures to ensure personal data will practically not be recoverable or reproducible. Data will specifically be deleted depending on how the data was collected, stored, and your interaction with Our Services. Digital documents containing personal data will be deleted via a technical method that will make it reasonably impossible to recover, retrieve, or become re-identifiable. Applika GmbH does not store personal data on non-digital documents or files.

**For Users Within California (CCPA/CPRA Area) and Virginia (VCDPA)**

**Categories of Personal Information Collected, Disclosed, or Sold**

We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular Consumer or Device.

Certain categories of personal information will only be collected if You provide such personal information directly to Us.

**Identifiers**: A unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers.

**Internet or other similar network activity:** Interaction with Our Service or advertisement.

**Geolocation data:** Approximate and precise physical location.

**Inferences** drawn from any of the Persona and Sensitive Personal Information listed above to create a profile or summary about, for example, an individual’s preferences and characteristics.

Applika GmbH only collects and makes use of the advertiser ID and the documentation on Your consent within Your Google account setting regarding personalized advertisements. Documentation on Your consent entails a unique ID, which is generated when You install the mobile application and make Your choice regarding advertisements. Applika GmbH cannot trace advertiser IDs or the unique ID related to a consent back to the identity of a specific user.

We obtain the categories of personal information listed above from the following categories of sources:

Directly from Your device when You install the App, or;

Indirectly via Your App-provider, if You have an application with Our Services integrated.

If We decide to collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information We collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes We will update this Privacy Policy.

**Use of Personal Information**

We may use or disclose personal information and sensitive personal information, We collect for “business purposes” or “commercial purposes”. For more details on how We use this information, please refer to the “Use of Your Data” section.

When We disclose personal information for a business purpose or a commercial purpose, We will enter into a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose except for performing the contract.

**Sale of Personal Information**

“Sell” and “sale” mean selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a consumer’s personal information by the business to a third party for valuable consideration.

This means that, for example, a sale can happen whenever an application runs ads or makes statistical analyses on the traffic or views.

**Opt-Out of Sale of Personal Information**

You have the right to opt out of the sale of Your personal information. Once We receive and confirm a verifiable consumer request from You, We will stop selling Your personal information. To exercise Your right to opt-out, please contact Us.

The Service Providers We partner with may use technology in the Service that sells personal information. If You wish to opt-out of the use of Your personal information for interest-based advertising purposes and these potential sales, You may do so on Your mobile device.

**Your Rights**

The VCDPA and CCPA/CPRA provides state residents with specific rights regarding their personal information. If You are a resident of any of these states, You have the following rights:

**The right to notice.** You have the right to be notified of which categories of Personal Data are being collected and the purposes for which the Personal Data is being used.

**The right to request.** You have the right to request that We disclose information to You about Our collection, use, sale, disclosure for business purposes, and share of personal information.

Once We receive and confirm Your request, We will disclose the information We have on You.

**The right to say no to the sale of Personal Data (opt-out).** You have the right to instruct Us to not sell Your personal information. To submit an opt-out request please contact Us.

**The right to delete Personal Data.** You have the right to request the deletion of Your Personal Data, subject to certain exceptions. Once We receive and confirm Your request, We will delete (and instruct Our Service Providers to delete) Your personal information from Our records, unless an exception applies. We may deny Your deletion request if retaining the information is deemed necessary for Us or Our Service Providers.

**The right not to be discriminated against.** You have the right not to be discriminated against for exercising any of Your consumer rights.

**The right to correct inaccurate personal information.** You have the right to request Us to correct any information about You that may be inaccurate.

**The right to limit the use and disclosure of Your sensitive personal information to that use which is necessary to perform the services or provide the goods.** Under CPRA You have the right to request We limit the use of Your sensitive personal information. Once We receive Your request, We will limit, and instruct Our Service Providers as well, the use of any sensitive personal information that may have been collected from You.

**Children’s Privacy**

Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 18.

**Exercise Your  Rights**

In order to exercise any of Your rights, and if You are a resident of California or Virginia, You can contact Us at [privacy@applika.ch](mailto:privacy@applika.ch)

**Your request to Us must:**

Provide sufficient information that allows Us to reasonably verify You are the person about whom We collected personal information, or that You are an authorized representative.

Describe Your request with sufficient detail that allows Us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to Your request or provide You with the required information if We cannot:

Verify Your identity or authority to make the request.

Confirm that the personal information relates to You

For data portability requests, We will select a format to provide Your personal information that is readily usable and should allow You to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to send us a contact us request to [privacy@applika.ch](mailto:privacy@applika.ch).

**Latest update: 17 July 2023**

Contact our support
-------------------

If you have any queries, issues, suggestions, or feedback feel free to drop us a message and we would get back to you as soon as possible.

* 

Your name \*\*  

Your email \*\*  

Subject  

Your message (facoltativo)  

\*\* We dont share your personal info with anyone. Check out our [Privacy Policy (Web site)](https://www.call-blocker.info/privacy-policy-web-site "Privacy Policy") for more information.

© 2023 Call Blocker - Caller ID - all rights reserved

We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.  

Do not sell my personal information.

Cookie SettingsAccept

Manage consent

Chiudi

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Sempre abilitato

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Durata | Descrizione |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-advertisement | 1 year | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Advertisement". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 1 year | This cookies is set by GDPR Cookie Consent WordPress Plugin. The cookie is used to remember the user consent for the cookies under the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 1 year | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 1 year | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| \_GRECAPTCHA | 5 months 27 days | This cookie is set by Google. In addition to certain standard Google cookies, reCAPTCHA sets a necessary cookie (\_GRECAPTCHA) when executed for the purpose of providing its risk analysis. |

Functional

 Functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 Performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

| Cookie | Durata | Descrizione |
| --- | --- | --- |
| YSC | session | This cookies is set by Youtube and is used to track the views of embedded videos. |

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Advertisement

 Advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

| Cookie | Durata | Descrizione |
| --- | --- | --- |
| IDE | 1 year 24 days | Used by Google DoubleClick and stores information about how the user uses the website and any other advertisement before visiting the website. This is used to present users with ads that are relevant to them according to the user profile. |
| test\_cookie | 15 minutes | This cookie is set by doubleclick.net. The purpose of the cookie is to determine if the user's browser supports cookies. |
| VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE | 5 months 27 days | This cookie is set by Youtube. Used to track the information of the embedded YouTube videos on a website. |

Others

 Others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

| Cookie | Durata | Descrizione |
| --- | --- | --- |
| CONSENT | 16 years 7 months 6 days 8 hours | No description |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 1 year | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 1 year | No description |

ACCETTA E SALVA

Powered by [](https://www.cookieyes.com/)
